vauxhall.co.uk 2005-12-16

# Vauxhall - Terms and Conditions of access

Copyright  
---  
Copyright 2004 General Motors Corporation. All Rights Reserved. All text, images, graphics, animation, videos, music and other materials on this website are subject to the copyright and other intellectual property rights of General Motors Corporation. These materials may not be reproduced, distributed, modified or reposted to other websites without the express written permission of General Motors Corporation.  
Trademark  
The marks appearing on this website including, but not limited to: (i) GM and the GM Logo; (ii) Chevrolet, Pontiac, Oldsmobile, Buick, Cadillac, GMC, Saturn and HUMMER and their respective logos, emblems, slogans and vehicle model names and body designs; and (iii) other marks such as Saab, Holden, Opel, Vauxhall, GMAC and ACDELCO are trademarks and/or service marks of General Motors Corporation, its subsidiaries, affiliates or licensors.  
Accessibility  
Vauxhall is committed to making its websites, accessible to all users. We are currently undertaking an extensive redevelopment to ensure that this website meets recognised accessibility standards.   
Notices  
The information contained herein is designed to be as comprehensive and factual as possible. We reserve the right, however, to make changes at any time, without notice, in prices, colours, materials, equipment, specifications, models and availability. 

Some links provided in this site may lead to sites furnished by independent site owners. The information presented therein is the sole responsibility of those site owners. GM and its advertising agencies have no control or responsibility for the content of independent sites and provides these links to its visitors for their convenience.   
  
Vauxhall WWW Site Terms and Conditions of Access  
This World Wide Website (the "Site") is operated by Vauxhall Motors Limited, a company registered under the Companies Acts in England (No. 135767) and having its registered office at Osborne Road, Luton, Bedfordshire ("Vauxhall").   
1\. Intellectual Property  
All materials within the Site are the intellectual property of Vauxhall. Such materials may not be copied or reproduced, save to the extent necessary to view the same on-line. However, you may print complete pages of the site to hard copy for your own personal use.  
Notwithstanding the generality of the foregoing, Vauxhall may from time to time give you the opportunity to download Wallpaper, Screen Savers and other utilities from the Site. Such downloads are covered by the Vauxhall Terms and Conditions of Download.  
2\. Linking to the Site  
If you wish to provide a link to the Site this must be to the **Vauxhall Homepage.**  
3\. Accuracy of Information  
This information in this site is intended for customers of Vauxhall in the United Kingdom and may not be applicable to other jurisdictions. Vauxhall will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that the contents of this Site are accurate and up to date. However, Vauxhall reserves the right to change product specifications at any time.   
NO RELIANCE SHOULD BE PLACED UPON ANY OF THE STATEMENTS MADE WITHIN THE SITE, AND VAUXHALL EXCLUDES TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW ALL LIABILITY (OTHER THAN LIABILITY FOR DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY) RESULTING FROM ANY SUCH RELIANCE.   
NOTWITHSTANDING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING, VAUXHALL EXCLUDES TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW ALL LIABILITY (OTHER THAN LIABILITY FOR DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY) RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE SITE.   
4\. Data Protection  
Vauxhall respects the privacy of every individual who visits the Site. This Clause 4 outlines the information Vauxhall may collect and store, and how it will be used.   
Personal Data  
Vauxhall will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (that is, your name, address, telephone number, or email address) ("Personal Data") unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your Personal Data collected, please do not submit it.   
If you have already submitted Personal Data and would like it removed from our records, please contact us at the email address or phone number listed at the bottom of this Clause 4. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our records.   
If you provide Vauxhall with Personal Data it will store this information about you now and in the future for marketing purposes, market research, tracking of sales data, and in order to contact you. Vauxhall may also disclose this information within its international group of companies (the GM Group, some of which are non-automotive) and to its retailers and agents for the above purposes.   
Non-Personally-Identifiable Information Collected Automatically  
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site or advertisement   
Information We May Place Automatically On Your Computer's Hard Drive  
When you view the Site we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor a website or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or visit the [About Cookies website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) to learn more about these functions.   
Whom to Contact  
If you have submitted Personal Data through the Site and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us at our e-mail address:  
or telephone the Customer Care Centre on (01582) 427200  
or write to The Customer Care Centre at Griffin House, Osborne Road, Luton, Bedfordshire LU1 3YT  
or click HERE.  
We will use reasonable efforts to delete this information from our existing files.  
5\. Law and Jurisdiction  
This site was created, and is operated, according to the laws of England. In determining any disputes in relation to this site the laws of England will apply and the Courts of England and Wales will have exclusive jurisdiction.   
VAUXHALL WWW SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF DOWNLOAD   
Vauxhall Motors Limited a company registered under the Companies Acts in England (No. 135767) and having its registered office at Osborne Road, Luton, Bedfordshire ("Vauxhall") hereby grants you a non-exclusive personal licence to use the materials downloadable from the site (the"Materials") subject always to the following conditions.

The Materials are the intellectual property of Vauxhall. You may not sub-licence, assign, transfer or sell the Materials or the rights granted hereunder. The Materials are provided "as is". Vauxhall excludes to the fullest extent permitted by law all warranties in relation to the Materials. 

The Materials on this site have been thoroughly scanned and tested at all stages of production. Notwithstanding this, we still recommend that you run a virus checker before use. We also recommend that you have an up-to-date backup of your hard disk before using the software. Vauxhall Motors Limited cannot accept responsibility for any disruption, damage and/or loss of data on your data or computer system that may occur while using the software. Consult your network administrator before downloading any Materials onto a networked computer.
